{
    "subject": "Warren_Beatty",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Reds__film_",
    "human_readable": "Warren Beatty directed the film Reds.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9596641659736633,
            "question": "Which of Warren Beatty's films is Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9264887571334839,
            "question": "Which film was directed by Warren Beatty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8829177618026733,
            "question": "Warren Beatty is known for directing which movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8676995038986206,
            "question": "Who directed the film Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8530464768409729,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Warren Beatty."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8278017044067383,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Warren Beatty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.816231369972229,
            "question": "Reds was directed by whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8080277442932129,
            "question": "What film did Warren Beatty helm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7475622892379761,
            "question": "What film is associated with Warren Beatty as a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6580257415771484,
            "question": "What movie did Warren Beatty direct?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warren Beatty directed the film Reds.",
            "html": "yago_21491_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film is associated with Warren Beatty as a director?",
            "html": "yago_21491_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Warren Beatty helm?",
            "html": "yago_21491_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Reds was directed by whom?",
            "html": "yago_21491_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21491_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Warren Beatty co-produced, directed, and wrote the film \"Reds,\" which directly supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}